Guide to the Committee on the Protection of Human Subjects, Yale University, Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Records, circa 1967-1983; Accession 1988-A-083
  - Black: The Organization of Narrative Information in Memory, 1980-1981 (Box 14, Folder 712)
  - Soloway: Bugs and Misconceptions of Novice Programmers, 1980-1981 (Box 14, Folder 713)
  - McKoon: Reading and the Acquisition of Knowledge, 1980-1981 (Box 14, Folder 714)
  - Scarr: Graduate Research Training in Child Psychology, 1980-1981 (Box 14, Folder 715)
  - Weinberger: Subjective Experience of Distress and Suppression of Personal Desires as Dimensions of Character Style, 1981-1982 (Box 14, Folder 716)
  - Pindar: Guilt in Employed Mothers and the Division of Family Work, 1981-1982 (Box 14, Folder 717)
  - Black: Representation, Use and Learning of Routine Knowledge, 1981-1982 (Box 14, Folder 718)
  - Soloway: Information Processing in Algebra and Computer Programming, 1981-1982 (Box 14, Folder 719)
  - Myers: The Epidemiology Catchment Area Program, 1981-1982 (Box 14, Folder 720)
  - Gordon: Implications of psychosocial and economic barriers impacting upon family units of the developmentally disabled: A model to alleviate some of the negative effects, 1981-1982 (Box 14, Folder 721)
  - Berman, Jr.: Attachment and Separation Distress in Post-Divorce Adjustment, 1981-1982 (Box 14, Folder 722)
  - Qualls: On the Consequences of repression: Accessibility of affective memories and the recognition of affect., 1981-1982 (Box 14, Folder 723)
  - Rabin: An Investigation of Recognition Memory for Odors, 1981-1982 (Box 14, Folder 724)
  - Bers: The Development of Social Comparison in Children, 1981-1982 (Box 14, Folder 725)
  - Samuel: Intervocalic consonant identification, 1981-1982 (Box 14, Folder 726)
  - Samuel: Speech Production, 1981-1982 (Box 14, Folder 727)
  - Linville: Mood States and the Self-Representation, 1981-1982 (Box 14, Folder 728)
  - Linville: Mood Variability and Representation of the Self, 1981-1982 (Box 14, Folder 729)
  - Linville: Responses to Positive and Negative Happenings, 1981-1982 (Box 14, Folder 730)
  - Soloway: The Design, Implementation, and Evaluation of an Intelligent Computer Instruction System for Programming, 1981-1982 (Box 14, Folder 731)
  - Scarr: Factors Affecting the Quality of Sibling Interaction, 1981-1982 (Box 14, Folder 732)
  - Hashimoto: The Elderly in Japan and America - a comparative community study, 1981-1982 (Box 14, Folder 733)
  - Soloway: Understanding the Root Concepts in Algebra and Computer Programming, 1981-1982 (Box 14, Folder 734)
  - Turk: Interpersonal Problem Solving, 1981-1982 (Box 14, Folder 735)
  - Hakutu: A Longitudinal Investigation of the Relationship between Bilingualism, Cognitive Flexibility, and Social-Cognitive Skills in Children, 1981-1982 (Box 14, Folder 736)
  - Wagner: Taste and Odor Identification, 1981-1982 (Box 14, Folder 737)
  - Singer: Clinical Psychology: Health and Child/Community, 1981-1982 (Box 14, Folder 738)
  - Silberstein: Conceptions of Health and Illness in Diabetic and Healthy Children, 1981-1982 (Box 14, Folder 739)
  - Sedlak: Impact of a Battered Woman's Shelter, 1981-1982 (Box 14, Folder 740)
  - Ratcliff: Order Relations in Perceptual Matching, 1981-1982 (Box 14, Folder 741)
  - Litt: Sources of Stress and Dissatisfaction in Public High School Teachers, 1981-1982 (Box 14, Folder 742)
  - Marcus: Influence of Variety in External Food Cues on Palatability and Consumption, 1981-1982 (Box 14, Folder 743)
  - Read: The Use of Single Instances in Causal Reasoning, 1981-1982 (Box 14, Folder 744)
  - Smith, Michael G.: Women and Men in Tonga, 1780-1980, 1981-1982 (Box 14, Folder 745)
  - Samuel: Phonemic Restoration: Individual Differences, Lexical Structures, and the Integration of Linguistic Knowledge, 1981-1982 (Box 14, Folder 746)
  - Bowen: Rigid and Flexible Self -Regulation of Cardiovascular Responses: Relationship to Emotion and Personality, 1981-1982 (Box 15, Folder 747)
  - Smith, Randy Turner: Dimensions of Family Process and Their Relation to Marital Adjustment, 1981-1982 (Box 15, Folder 748)
  - Reiss, Jr.: Social Science Research Training: The Sociology of Social Control, 1981-1982 (Box 15, Folder 749)
  - Pino: Family Dynamics Under Various Task Conditions, 1981-1982 (Box 15, Folder 750)
  - Berndt: The Assessment of Developmental Changes in Friendship, 1981-1982 (Box 15, Folder 751)
  - Terrell: Academic Success and Coping in Disadvantaged Black Students, 1981-1982 (Box 15, Folder 752)
  - Myers: The Epidemiology Catchment Area Program, 1981-1982 (Box 15, Folder 753)
  - Scarr: Graduate Research Training in Child Psychology, 1981-1982 (Box 15, Folder 754)
  - Crowder: The Major/Minor Distinction in Music Cognition, 1981-1982 (Box 15, Folder 755)
  - Salter: A Study of Tacit Theories of Economics, 1981-1982 (Box 15, Folder 756)
  - Rodin: Changes in Taste Responsiveness in Pregnancy, 1981-1982 (Box 15, Folder 757)
  - Tischler: Training Program in Mental Health Services Research and Evaluation, 1981-1982 (Box 15, Folder 758)
  - Repetti: The Role of the Interpersonal Climate at Work on Psychological Well Being and Family Relations, 1981-1982 (Box 15, Folder 759)
  - Garner: Perception of Structure, 1981-1982 (Box 15, Folder 760)
  - Spitzer: The Effects of Ingesting Different Types of Nutrients on Taste, 1981-1982 (Box 15, Folder 761)
  - Serafine: Memory for Melody and Text in Songs, 1981-1982 (Box 15, Folder 762)
  - Linville: Organization of Information about Ingroups and Outgroups, 1981-1982 (Box 15, Folder 763)
  - Swalin: Nationalism, Democracy and Development: the Conflict Between Integration, Autonomy and Separation in Puerto Rico, 1981-1982 (Box 15, Folder 764)
  - Iyengar: An Information-processing Analysis of Media Agenda-Setting, 1981-1982 (Box 15, Folder 765)
  - Kahn: Representation of Self and Others, 1981-1982 (Box 15, Folder 766)
  - Salovey: Perceived Variability of Ingroups and Outgroups, 1981-1982 (Box 15, Folder 767)
  - Lipian: Visual and Auditory Expertise and Preference, 1981-1982 (Box 15, Folder 768)
  - Allen: Social Evaluation of the Fox Lane Middle School, 1981-1982 (Box 15, Folder 770)
  - Sussman: Assessment of a Middle School Self-study, 1981-1982 (Box 15, Folder 771)
  - Salovey: Social Comparison and Feelings of Envy, 1981-1982 (Box 15, Folder 772)
  - Bernstein: An Exploration into Personality and the Self, 1981-1982 (Box 15, Folder 773)
  - Miller: An Investigation of Social and Political Attitudes of High School Students, 1981-1982 (Box 15, Folder 774)
  - Berndt: Friendships as Social Supports for Children during School Transitions, 1981-1982 (Box 15, Folder 775)
  - Myers: The Epidemiology Catchment Area Program, 1981-1982 (Box 15, Folder 776)
  - Swanson: The Missionary Life-World: A Paradign of Social and Spiritual Estrangement, 1981-1982 (Box 15, Folder 777)
  - Pinderhughes: Factors Influencing Families' Participation in a Bonding Program, 1981-1982 (Box 15, Folder 778)
  - McGuire: Content, Structure, and Functioning of Brief Systems, 1981-1982 (Box 15, Folder 779)
  - Crits-Christoph: "Interactions of Environmental Stress, Chronic Anger, and Biological Risk Factors in Essential Hypertension", 1981-1982 (Box 15, Folder 780)
  - Soloway: A Computer-Based Program Introductory Programming, 1981-1982 (Box 15, Folder 781)
  - Goncebate: "Comparative Social Change; The Political Parties in Argentina, Chile, and Uruguay 1970-1974", 1981-1982 (Box 15, Folder 782)
  - Black: Intelligent Computer Assisted Instruction: An Interactive Reading, 1981-1982 (Box 15, Folder 783)
  - Scarr: Graduate Research Training in Child Psychology, 1981-1982 (Box 15, Folder 784)
  - Cauce: Adolescent Social Networks and Networking: Contributions to Social Competency, 1981-1982 (Box 15, Folder 785)
  - Abelson: Program in Social Psychological Problems, 1981-1982 (Box 15, Folder 786)
  - Piotrkowski: Job Stress and children's Mental Health: An Ecological Study, 1981-1982 (Box 15, Folder 787)
- Records, 1982-1988; Accession 1990-A-065
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2023.
  - Gersick: Life Cycles of Temporary Work Groups, 1982-1983 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Sternberg: Components of Verbal Intelligence, 1982-1983 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Sternberg: Insight in the Gifted, 1982-1983 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Grajek: Correlates and Dimensions of Sibling Interaction in Middle Childhood, 1982-1983 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Schwartz: "Health Psychology: Clinical and Preventive Research", 1982-1983 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Hakuta: "A Demographic Study of the Hispanic Population in New Haven". WITHDRAWN, 1982-1983 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Salovey: "Cognitions about Health and Illness", 1982-1983 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Linville: Self-Complexity as a Moderator o f Recent Life Events, 1982-1983 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Crowder: See #871, 1982-1983 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Singer, Jefferson: "Emotion, Facial Expression, and Imagery"., 1982-1983 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Singer, Jefferson: Imagery, Sensory Stimuli, and Facial Expressions, 1982-1983 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Hewett: The role of individual differences and emotional tone in children's cognitive processing and performance, 1982-1983 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Peters: Vividness, Distraction, and Persuasion, 1982-1983 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Piotrkowski: "Job Stressors and Mental Health", 1982-1983 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Greene: "Long-Term Modality Effects'', 1982-1983 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Hoblitzelle: "Developing a Measure of Shame and Guilt'', 1982-1983 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Sternberg: "The Nature of Intelligence over the Adult Life Span", 1982-1983 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Rollock: "Factors in the Response to Racial Discrimination'', 1982-1983 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Bybee: "Effects of self-generated Versus Externally Presented Information on Attitude", 1982-1983 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Piotrkowski: "Attitudes toward Job Involved Men and Women", 1982-1983 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Pino-Piotrkowski: "Family Dynamics Under Various Task Conditions", 1982-1983 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Reiss, Jr.: "Social Science Research Training: The Sociology of Social Control", 1982-1983 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Greene: "Reading Instruction and Reasoning", 1982-1983 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Shiller: "An Investigation of the Adjustment to Latency Age Boys in Joint Custody Arrangements", 1982-1983 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Crosby: "Denial of Personal Discrimination", 1982-1983 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Muller: ''Career/Family Patterns Among Ph.D Recipients", 1982-1983 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Anhier: "The Development Potential of Indigenous Voluntary Associations for Social and Development in Urban Areas: Nigeria", 1982-1983 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Kessen: "Graduate Research Training in Child Psychology", 1982-1983 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Weinshenker: "The Effects of Adolescent Disappofntment Experiences on Adult Coping Skills", 1982-1983 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Hawkins: "Emotion in Friendship", 1982-1983 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Singer and Singer: "Television and Family Living Patterns", 1982-1983 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Tischler: "Mental Health Services Research", 1982-1983 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Ward: "Priming between Label-congruent and Label-incongruent Facts", 1982-1983 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Rosenberg: "Openness to Sexual Experience", 1982-1983 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Wagner: "A Comparison of Facial EMG and of Subjective Quality of 'Primary' and 'Complex' Emotions", 1982-1983 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Loewenstein: "Expectations of Uncertain Future Outcomes", 1982-1983 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Whitehorn: "Modulation of Baroreceptor Reflex by Emotional state", 1982-1983 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Marcus: "Effect of Price, Product Composition, Intersample Interval, and Expectations on Quality Perceptions of Wine", 1982-1983 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Garner: "Perception of Structure", 1982-1983 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Rodin: "Dietary habits, social factors, stress and health in aging", 1982-1983 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Singer: "Child and Adolescent Clinical/Community Psychology: Training in Direct Service and Prevention Programming", 1982-1983 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Callaghan: "The Development of Perceptual Organization", 1982-1983 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Crosby: "Domestic Distress and Response Syndromes at Work", 1982-1983 (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Turk: "Chronic Low Back Pain: Evaluation of a Stress-Diathesis Model", 1982-1983 (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Soloway: "The Generality of schemata cross Different Types of Texts: InformationRepresentation and Processing Strategies'', 1982-1983 (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Soloway: "Mappings between Programmers' Conceptualizations and Programming Language Constructs", 1982-1983 (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Burrell: "Teacher Satisfaction: The Economicand Social Aspects", 1982-1983 (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Schorr: "Decision-Making in Real Life Situations", 1982-1983 (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - McGuire: "Content, Structure and Functioning of Belief Systems", 1982-1983 (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - Tromley: "The Strategies Groups Use to Deal with Deviant Members", 1982-1983 (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - Rosekind: "PsychophysiologicaI Responses to Emotional Imagery in Narcoleptics and Normals", 1982-1983 (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - Janis: "Program in Social Psychological Problems", 1982-1983 (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - Fetter: Classification System, 1982-1983 (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - Singer: "Health Psychology: Clinical and Preventive Health'', 1982-1983 (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - Rodin: "Changes in Taste Responsiveness in Pregnancy", 1982-1983 (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - Piotrkowski: "Occupational Stress: Workplace Factors in Psychological strain", 1982-1983 (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - Piotrkowski: "The Contribution of Battering to Alcoholism Among Women", 1982-1983 (Box 2, Folder 57)
  - Pindar: "Pilot Study for Research on Adolescents' Modes of Social Explanation", 1982-1983 (Box 2, Folder 58)
  - Schwartz: "Relaxing Effects of Meditation and Fragrance." Approved, 1982-1983 (Box 2, Folder 59)
  - Weissberg: "The Relationship of Problern-Solving, Interpersonal Values, and School Performance in 7th and 8th Graders'', 1982-1983 (Box 2, Folder 60)
  - Tischler: "Mental Health Services Research Training Program", 1982-1983 (Box 2, Folder 62)
  - Soloway: "Transfer Effects of Computer Programrning", 1982-1983 (Box 2, Folder 63)
  - Weissberg: See #896, 1982-1983 (Box 2, Folder 64)
  - Rodin: "Gravid Food Behavior, Infant Responsiveness and Weight Gain", 1982-1983 (Box 2, Folder 65)
  - Barker: "Banks and the Financing of Industry: The Determinants, and Impact of Credit Allocation in the Socio-Economic Development of Brazil", 1983-1984 (Box 3, Folder 66)
  - Medvene: "Case Studies of Voluntary and Paid Helpers", 1983-1984 (Box 3, Folder 67)
  - Hawkins: "Friendship as Social Supports for Children during School Transitions", 1983-1984 (Box 3, Folder 68)
  - Repetti: "The Interpersonal Climate at Work: Its Importance to Employees and its Relationship to Their Psychological Well-Being", 1983-1984 (Box 3, Folder 69)
  - Telgarsky: "Individual Responses to the Perception of Symptoms and Bodily Sensations.", 1983-1984 (Box 3, Folder 71)
  - Marsh: "Attitudes toward the Right to Refuse Life-Enhancing Help or Treatment", 1983-1984 (Box 3, Folder 72)
  - McGuire: "Content, Structure and Functioning of Thought Systems", 1983-1984 (Box 3, Folder 73)
  - Clayton: "Perceptions of Job Discrimination", 1983-1984 (Box 3, Folder 74)
  - Rosenberg: "Attitudes about sex", 1983-1984 (Box 3, Folder 75)
  - Miller: "Quits and Fires: A Study of Former Police Officers in an Urban Police Organization", 1983-1984 (Box 3, Folder 76)
  - Leit: "The Influence of Personality on Future Career Choices and Health Care Practices", 1983-1984 (Box 3, Folder 77)
  - Crits-Christoph: "Development of Measures to Assess Styles of Coping with Negative Emotions: Reliability and Validity Analysis", 1983-1984 (Box 3, Folder 78)
  - Mishkind: "Decision Making by Gay Men about Their Sexual Behavior in Response to AIDS", 1983-1984 (Box 3, Folder 79)
  - Singer, J. and Singer, D.: "Television and Family Living Patterns", 1983-1984 (Box 3, Folder 80)
  - Clayton: "Making Inferential Decisions", 1983-1984 (Box 3, Folder 81)
  - Soloway: "Understanding the Bugs and Misconceptions of Novice Programmers'', 1983-1984 (Box 3, Folder 82)
  - Hackman: "The Design and Management of Work Teams", 1983-1984 (Box 4, Folder 83)
  - Barnes: "Personality Correlates of Self-Complexity", 1983-1984 (Box 4, Folder 84)
  - Schwartz: "Psychophysiology of Facial Expression and Emotion", 1983-1984 (Box 4, Folder 85)
  - Gochberg: "Patterns of Affective Fluctuation throughout the Menstrual Cycle: A New Approach'', 1983-1984 (Box 4, Folder 86)
  - Komatsu: "Children's Understanding of Conventions, Laws, and Logical Popositions", 1983-1984 (Box 4, Folder 87)
  - Samuel: "Insights from a Length Dependence of the Word Advantage", 1983-1984 (Box 4, Folder 88)
  - Samuel: "Speech: Perceptual, Decision, and Attentional Factors", 1983-1984 (Box 4, Folder 89)
  - Reiss: "Social Science Research Training", 1983-1984 (Box 4, Folder 90)
  - Zigler: "Role of Motivation in the Test Performance of Disadvantaged Children", 1983-1984 (Box 4, Folder 91)
  - Stuart: "Mood Induction by Self-Generated Imagery", 1983-1984 (Box 4, Folder 92)
  - Feldman: "Context Effects in Bilingualism", 1983-1984 (Box 4, Folder 93)
  - Schwartz and Gochberg: "The Effects of Heavy and Light Imagery on Time Perception and the Rate ofPhysiological Clocks", 1983-1984 (Box 4, Folder 94)
  - Singer: "Child and Adolescent Clinical/Community Psychology: Training in Direct Service and Prevention Programming", 1983-1984 (Box 4, Folder 95)
  - Soloway: "Cognitive Factors in Design", 1983-1984 (Box 4, Folder 96)
  - Comer: "Individual Effort Toward a Group Task", 1983-1984 (Box 4, Folder 97)
  - Zigler: "Assessing Head Start: Its Effectiveness and Impact on Head Start and non Head Start Children and Families", 1983-1984 (Box 4, Folder 98)
  - Schank: "Automated Medical Information and Diagnostic System", 1983-1984 (Box 4, Folder 99)
  - Soloway: "Transfer Effects of Computer Programming", 1983-1984 (Box 4, Folder 100)
  - Dreisen: "Language and Attitude Change", 1983-1984 (Box 4, Folder 101)
  - Clayton: "Perceptions of Discrimination", 1983-1984 (Box 4, Folder 102)
  - Dunlap: "Ethical Reasoning about Animal Treatmnt and Its Relationship to Moral Development", 1983-1984 (Box 4, Folder 103)
  - Weissberg and Krauss: "Evaluation of the Growth Center: A School-based Mental Health Program for the Early Detection and Prevention of School Maladjustment in Young Children", 1983-1984 (Box 4, Folder 104)
  - Nicol: ''PSPQ Validation Study", 1983-1984 (Box 4, Folder 105)
  - Turner: "Dimensions of Family Systems and Their Relation to Adolescent Functioning", 1983-1984 (Box 4, Folder 106)
  - Pino: "Priming with TAT Pictures: A Pilot Study", 1983-1984 (Box 4, Folder 107)
  - Garner: "Perception of Structure", 1983-1984 (Box 4, Folder 108)
  - Paul: "Participation in Hospital Decision-Making", 1983-1984 (Box 4, Folder 109)
  - Crosby: "Stress and coping of working, divorced parents", 1983-1984 (Box 4, Folder 110)
  - Nicol: "Children Learning Logo", 1983-1984 (Box 4, Folder 111)
  - Crowder: "Memory Representation in Auditory Cognition", 1983-1984 (Box 4, Folder 112)
  - Striegel-Moore: "Bulimic Individuals' Exprience of Emotions in Experimental and Naturalistic Situations", 1983-1984 (Box 4, Folder 113)
  - Herek: "Opinions about Controversial Issues", 1983-1984 (Box 4, Folder 114)
  - Baldwin: "Automatic Evaluation of Design Choices in Digital Controller Design", 1983-1984 (Box 4, Folder 115)
  - Pinderhughes: "Characteristics of Hard-to-Place Children and Short Tem Outcome of Adoptions", 1983-1984 (Box 4, Folder 116)
  - Wolpe: "Professions and Ideology: An examination of the Holistic Health Movement", 1983-1984 (Box 4, Folder 117)
  - Kahn: "Sensing Humor", 1983-1984 (Box 4, Folder 118)
  - Rosekind: "Sleep/Wake Patterns in Shiftworkers", 1983-1984 (Box 4, Folder 119)
  - Fetter: "Management Control Processes in Product Development", 1983-1984 (Box 4, Folder 120)
  - Ferdman: "Attitudes towards Jesse Jackson", 1983-1984 (Box 4, Folder 121)
  - Adelson: "Problem Solving Strategies in Program Comprehension and Generation", 1983-1984 (Box 4, Folder 122)
  - Braginsky: "Expendability Scale Development", 1983-1984 (Box 4, Folder 123)
  - Zigum: "An Investigation into Perception without Awareness: Tachistoscopic Presentation of Emotionally Charged Scenes within a Movie", 1983-1984 (Box 5, Folder 124)
  - Foster: "Models of English in Two Comanche Communities: An Ethnographic Study of Speech in Social Interaction", 1983-1984 (Box 5, Folder 125)
  - Soloway: "Program Documentation: Theory and Experiment", 1983-1984 (Box 5, Folder 126)
  - Soloway: "A Cognitive Model of Program Understanding", 1983-1984 (Box 5, Folder 127)
  - Hodapp: "Implicit Theories of Mental Retardation", 1983-1984 (Box 5, Folder 128)
  - Fetter: "Development of an Ambulatory Patient Classification System'', 1983-1984 (Box 5, Folder 129)
  - Samuel: "Levels of Analysis of Complex Auditory Stimuli'', 1983-1984 (Box 5, Folder 130)
  - Abelson: "Program in Social Psychological Problems", 1983-1984 (Box 5, Folder 131)
  - Hakuta: "Transfer of Skills across Language in Bilingual Children", 1983-1984 (Box 5, Folder 132)
  - Abelson: "Cognitive Processes in Survey Responding", 1983-1984 (Box 5, Folder 133)
  - Wilkinson: "Investigation into Family Variables Associated with Social Problem-Solving Abilities: of Mentally Retarded and Average Intelligence Social Children", 1983-1984 (Box 5, Folder 134)
  - Rodin: "Dietary Habits, Social Factors, Stress, and Health in Aging", 1983-1984 (Box 5, Folder 135)
  - Zigler: "Cognitive, Motivational and Environmental Determinants of Functioning in Retarded Individuals", 1983-1984 (Box 5, Folder 136)
  - Weissberg: "Promoting Social Competence and Coping Skills in Young Adolescents: Assessment, Intervention and Long-Term Follow-up", 1983-1984 (Box 5, Folder 137)
  - Myers: "The Epidemiology Catchment Area Program", 1983-1984 (Box 5, Folder 138)
  - Schwartz: "The Effects of Imagery on Time Perception and Relaxing Effects of Fragrance'', 1984-1985 (Box 5, Folder 139)
  - Schaffer: "Relations Between Anaclitic/Introjective Personality Dimensions and Cognitive Style", 1984-1985 (Box 5, Folder 140)
  - Schwartz: "Ease of Learning Correctly Versus Incorrectly Translated Paired Associates", 1984-1985 (Box 5, Folder 141)
  - Medvene: "Case Studies of Voluntary and Paid Helpers", 1984-1985 (Box 5, Folder 142)
  - Kessen: "Graduate Training in Child Psychology", 1984-1985 (Box 5, Folder 143)
  - Schwartz: "ARC Pilot Study-Hedenics", 1984-1985 (Box 5, Folder 144)
  - Zigler: "Probability Learning in Organically Retarded Famially Retarded and Normal Children'', 1984-1985 (Box 5, Folder 145)
  - Widner: "Harambee, Ethnic Loyalties, and the Sources of Kenyan Political Stability", 1984-1985 (Box 5, Folder 146)
  - Timko "Women's Decisions to Seek Medical Care", 1984-1985 (Box 5, Folder 147)
  - Miller: "Judgments of Everyday Social Behavior", 1984-1985 (Box 5, Folder 148)
  - Zigler: "The Relationship between Selective Attention and Outerdirectedness in Retarded and Nonretarded Children", 1984-1985 (Box 5, Folder 149)
  - Rosenberg: "The Relationship Between Sexual Fantasy and Sexual Behavior", 1984-1985 (Box 5, Folder 150)
  - Reiss, Jr.: "Mental Health and Social Control'', 1984-1985 (Box 5, Folder 151)
  - Zigler: "Social Competence and Psychopathology in Mentally Retarded Adults", 1984-1985 (Box 5, Folder 152)
  - Silberstein: "The Dual-Career Marriage: A System in Transition", 1984-1985 (Box 5, Folder 153)
  - Bybee: "Classroom Behavior: Its Relationship to the Development of Guilt in Children", 1984-1985 (Box 5, Folder 154)
  - Leit: "Undifferentiated and Differentiated Cardiovascular Patterns in Children", 1984-1985 (Box 5, Folder 155)